http://www.thetrumpet.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
The www.theTrumpet.com site is produced and sponsored by the Philadelphia Church of God, Inc. (pcg). The pcg collects personally identifiable information which is specifically and voluntarily provided by visitors to pcg's website. In addition, the pcg also collects non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies, third-party analytics tools and similar technology.
A visitor may choose to provide personally identifiable information in the following examples:
Subscribing to newsletters or publications, digital and print
Ordering literature
Creating an account to manage subscriptions and orders
Corresponding with staff for further information or comment
Non-personally identifiable information does not reveal a person's identity or directly relate to an individual, on its own. It may include the type of browser being used (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc), the type of operating system being used (e.g., Windows, Mac OS X, etc), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., msn, Earthlink, etc), and general geographic location.
HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION
When a visitor provides personally identifiable information to us, the pcg uses it for the purpose for which it was provided at the point of collection (or as obvious from the context of the collection). This includes processing literature requests, sending e-mail newsletters, and communicating with a user who has identified themselves. Those purposes may include follow-up information and promotional offers necessary for providing services to users.
The pcg uses non-personally identifiable information to improve the design and content of theTrumpet.com and to enable the pcg to personalize a user's Internet experience. The information may be summarized into reports for the purposes of analyzing site usage.
The pcg may share non-personally identifiable information with pre-screened third parties for marketing or promotional purposes. This information is collected through a unique cookie, pixel tag or similar technology and is anonymous to us. See the "Cookies" section to learn more about how that is shared. The pcg uses this information to deliver promotions of our services to website visitors, or users who are similar to website visitors, through a third-party partner.
The pcg reserves the right to disclose personal information, when the pcg believes in good faith that disclosure is legally required, to protect our rights and/or the safety of others.
The pcg restricts access to collected information and requires that it only be used as required for the purposes of fulfilling the services offered by the pcg.
The pcg does not sell or otherwise distribute information to third parties except as previously described.
The pcg retains personally identifiable information for as long as needed to provide service to them, or as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
COOKIES
The pcg uses "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. This file is accessed, for example, to determine previously established viewing preferences. Cookies are not used to gain personal information that is not specifically supplied by the user.
The configuration of most browsers is initially set to accept cookies. Browsers can be set to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are sent. However, preventing the use of cookies may inhibit the designed functionality of the site.
The pcg also uses cookies, and similar technology such as pixel tags, from marketing partners, analytics providers, social media platforms and other third parties. These cookies are not used to gain personal information and are anonymous to the pcg unless specifically supplied by the user.
For more information of the third-party tools we use and what information they collect, review our Third-Party Disclosure.
THIRD-PARTY LINKS
The pcg may provide links to third-party sites for the purpose of enhancing the viewing experience, for crediting sources, for providing access to needed browser plug-ins, or for other purposes. Third-party sites may have different privacy policies and methodologies for protecting collected information. Viewers of these sites should be aware of this difference and read available privacy statements.
GDPR RIGHTS
EU citizens have the legal right to:
Request information as to whether or not, and to what extent, the pcg processes their personal data.
Correct their personal data.
Delete their personal data.
Restrict the processing of their personal data.
Request their personal data collected by the pcg.
Object to processing of their personal data under certain circumstances.
Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if they believe the processing of your personal data constitutes an infringement of the provisions of the gdpr.
EU citizens may contact us directly to do so.
CONTACT US
If you have questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete or change any personal information we hold, please e-mail info@pcog.org.
You may also contact us via mail:
Using this site signifies your agreement to terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement.
The pcg reserves the right to change this policy at any time without prior notice or notification.
